

# OKSANA VLASENKO

# Senior Frontend Developer

+38(063)-582-9166 vlasenkoksenia642@gmail.com

https://oksanavlasenko.github.io/vlasenko/

### **EDUCATION**

Master degree of CyberSecurity

V. N. Karazin Kharkiv National University

2006 - 2008

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

Official EF SET Certificate | Oksana Vlasenko | C2 (72/100)

## **GITHUB**

https://github.com/oksana Vlasenko

## **SKILLS**

- Vue 2, 3
- VUEX
- Tailwind CSS
- Vue Router
- Solid.js
- React
- JavaScript
- HTML / CSS
- SCSS
- i18n

#### LANGUAGE

- Ukrainian Native
- English Advanced

## **PROFILE**

I'm a software developer with 4+ years of web development. I'm proficient in JavaScript, Vue 2, and have worked with Vue 3, Node.js, Express,js, Tailwind CSS, TypeScript etc. I have been working with Vue 2 over 3 years. My goal is delivering the best possible user experience, performance, and intuitiveness in the products I develop.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **FixIQ Pro**

2021.09 - 2024.07

Frontend Developer

- Develop new features, maintain codebase, and perform code reviews.
- Part of a team creating a micro front-end using Solid.js.
- · Mentor junior developers
- Technologies: Vue 2, Vuex, Vue Router, Solid.js

#### **Medstar Solutions**

2021.06 - 2021.09

Frontend Developer

- Worked on a Vue 2 application.
- Created new components, maintained features, and wrote unit tests with Jest.

#### **Freelance**

2020.07 - 2021.05

Frontend Developer

• Worked with the MERN stack, Vue 2, React, and native JavaScript...

#### Varion

2020.01 - 2020.04

Junior Frontend Developer

- Developed games with Phaser.js
- Developed new features with Vue 2 and native JavaScript

#### **REFERENCES**

#### Roman Almazov

**Edison Donets** Lead QA Engineer

Lead Frontend Engineer

Telegram: @edison\_edison05

Telegram: @ralmaz